<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>ConnorTheVGFan78's Blog</title>
  <description>A blog created by ConnorTheVGFan78</description>
  <link>https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/</link>
  <atom:link href="https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 12:47:40 -0400</lastBuildDate>
  <ttl>60</ttl>

<!-- ADD NEW POST HERE -->

  <item>
    <title>An Old Survey: Online Communities</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[      <div id="content-warning">
        <br>
        <br>
        <h3>Content Warning:</h3>
        <p>This post re-uses content from an <a href="https://connorthevgfan78.blogspot.com/2020/02/the-results-of-online-communities.html" target="_blank">older post</a> on my original <a href="https://connorthevgfan78.blogspot.com/" target="_blank">Blogger Page</a>. Certain edits may have been made to conform this post to my current writing style, and to correct inaccuracies / grammar mistakes that the original post may have contained.</p>
      </div>

            <p>In late 2019, I did a school project for a college English class that went into detail about online communities and how they affect people.</p>

            <p>Along with this project, I conducted a survey to help prove my points and gather information from the public. I posted a link to the survey on my Twitter, Instagram Story, in a couple Discord Servers, and a platform I used to use called Amino to get as many people to answer the survey as possible. In the end, only 7 people responded to the survey. Here were the results:</p>

            <h2>Question 1: Are you part of an online community that focuses on (a) certain topic(s)?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-1.PNG" alt="Pie Chart: Yes 85.7%; No 14.3%">

            <p>Only one of the seven respondents of this survey said no to this question. This question was used mainly as a demographic question to gauge how many people doing the survey were part of a community centered around a central topic.</p>

            <h2>Question 2: Why do you usually join an online community?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-2.PNG" alt="Bar Chart: To find new people who share a similar interest 5; To make new friends 7; To share your opinions on a certain topic 1; To gain new information on a topic you're interested in 2">

            <p>This was a question that accepted multiple answers at once.</p>

            <p>Everyone who responded to this question said that they mainly join a community to make friends. Five people said that they join an online community to find people with similar interests. Two people say that they join a community to gain new information on a topic. One person said that they join communities to share opinions on a topic.</p>

            <h2>Question 3: What platform would you most likely use?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-3.PNG" alt="Bar Chart: Twitter 3; Reddit 3; Discord 5; Amino 3; Tumblr 1; Instagram 2">

            <p>This was another question that accepted multiple answers at once.</p>

            <p>Five of the respondents said they would use Discord to join an online community. Three people said they would use either Twitter, Reddit, or Amino. Two people said they would use Instagram. One person said they would use Tumblr.</p>

            <h2>Question 4: How much do you like being in a community?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-4.PNG" alt="Bar Chart: Strongly Dislike 1; Neutral 1; Slightly Like 4">

            <p>Respondents were given a scale from 1 to 5 to rate how much they like being in an online community, with 1 being “Strongly Dislike” and 5 being “Strongly Like”.</p>

            <p>One person rated it a 1. Another person rated it a 3. Five others rated it a 4.</p>

            <h2>The Online Community Life Cycle</h2>

            <p>In my school project, I described the life cycle of online community membership as follows:</p>
            <ul style="text-align:left;">
            <li><b>Lurker</b> (Pretty self explanatory; Someone who doesn't contribute to the community and 'lurks')</li>
            <li><b>Newbie</b> (Someone who's relatively new to contributing to the community)</li>
            <li><b>Regular</b> (Someone who posts regularly in a community)</li>
            <li><b>Leader</b> (Someone who has reached 'celebrity status' within a community or someone who moderates a community)</li>
            <li><b>Elder</b> (Someone who is preparing to leave a community based on changes of interests, relationships, etc.)</li>
            </ul>
            <h2>Question 5: What stage of the life cycle are you at?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-5.PNG" alt="Pie Chart: Lurker 42.9%; Newbie 28.6%; Regular 28.6%">

            <p>Respondents were asked what stage of the life cycle they were currently at within the community they were most active.</p>
            <p>Three people considered themselves Lurkers. Two people considered themselves Newbies. Two others considered themselves Regulars.</p>

            <h2>Question 6: What stages of the life cycle have you experienced?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-6.PNG" alt="Bar Chart: Lurker 6; Newbie 5; Regular 6; Leader 2; Elder 2">

            <p>Respondents were asked what stages of the life cycle they have experienced personally. This was a multi-answer question.</p>

            <p>Six respondents said they've experienced the Lurker and Regular stages. Five said they've experienced the Newbie stage. Two have said they've experienced the Leader and Elder stages.</p>

            <h2>Question 7: Is this life cycle accurate?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-7.PNG" alt="Pie Chart: Yes 85.7%; No 14.3%">

            <p>Respondents were asked if the life cycle was accurate to how people enter, interact with, and exit a community.</p>

            <p>Only one of the seven respondents said that the life cycle was not accurate, while the remaining six respondents said that it was accurate.</p>

            <h2>Question 8: Have commitments in online communities changed the way you approach IRL socialization?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-8.PNG" alt="Pie Chart: Yes 28.6%; No 57.1%; Maybe 14.3%">

            <p>Respondents were asked if a commitment to an online community had ever drastically changed how they interacted with people in real life.</p>
            <p>Four people said that it didn't. Two people said that it did. One person was unsure.</p>

            <h2>Question 9: Do you agree that people can form lasting relationships online?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-9.PNG" alt="Pie Chart: Strongly Agree 28.6%; Agree 42.9%; Neutral 14.3%; Strongly Disagree 14.3%;">

            <p>Respondents were asked if they agreed with the statement "Online communities can help bring people together and make long, lasting relationships."</p>

            <p>Three people said that they slightly agreed with the statement. Two people said that they strongly agree with the statement. One person was neutral about the statement. One person strongly disagreed with the statement.</p>

            <h2>Question 10: Do you agree that you must be careful with who you trust online?</h2>

            <img src="/images/posts/2024-09-03/Survey-10.PNG" alt="Pie Chart: Strongly Agree 28.6%; Agree 57.1%; Neutral 14.3%">

            <p>Respondents were asked if they agreed with the statement "You must be very careful with who you trust in an online community."</p>

            <p>Four people slightly agreed with the statement. Two people strongly agreed with the statement. One person was neutral about the statement.</p>

            <h2>Additional Comments from Respondents</h2>
            <p>Respondents were asked at the end of the survey to give additional comments about online communities. Only four people gave additional comments.</p>
            
            <p>One person said that "Online communities are great but there may be a downside to them, in which they could also be toxic."</p>

            <p>Another person said that online communities could cause damage to one's mental health, citing cyberbullying.</p>

            <p>The person who strongly disagreed with Question 9's statement said "Show me just one person who made a lasting friendship on the Internet. Impossible, isn't it?"</p>

            <p>Finally, another person said that "Online communities are great but there may be a downside to them, in which they could also be toxic."</p>

            <h2>Research Conclusion</h2>

            <p>The results of the survey helped me not only with my school project, but in understanding how other people felt about online interaction. I hope that the results of this survey can benefit others with their research or with understanding why people like/dislike online communities.</p>

            <h2>Reflecting On The Survey 5 Years Later</h2>

            <p>When I conducted this survey back in 2019, I was hoping to have a sizable enough sample size to justify my findings. Unfortunately, I feel that a sample size of only 7 people wasn’t big enough to get a feel for how the Internet as a whole feels about online communities. I hope to be able to do a survey like this in the future with a much bigger sample size.</p>

            <p>Additionally, I feel that some questions were worded improperly (the original Question 4 text is a bit confusing to read, using “like/dislike” instead of just “like”). Had some of the questions been worded properly, I feel that respondents would have had an easier time answering them.</p>

            <p>Overall, I feel the survey could have done better with a larger sample size and different wording in the question set. I hope to get the opportunity to do a survey like this again someday, whether it be for school research or another purpose. With how much online interaction has changed within the past 5 years (especially with the rise of remote work during the COVID-19 Pandemic), I feel that a proper sequel to this survey is overdue.</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <link>https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/posts/2024-09-03-An-Old-Survey--Online-Communities.html</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/feed.xml#2</guid>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>Wow, a MAJOR UPDATE!!!</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p>Oh wow, is this a dream? Are we in another dimension? Did Zefram Cochrane invent Warp Drive 39 Years early to let us travel the galaxy and discover a website that’s <b>this</b> level of “out of this world”???</p>
            
            <p>Nope, I just updated the appearance of my website. And wow does it look <b>WAY</b> better!! Let’s look at the two side by side:</p>
            <div><div style="float: left;width:300px;text-align:center;"><img src="/images/posts/2024-08-21/old-main.jpg" width="250px"><p><font size="1"><i>Out with the old...</i></font></p></div><div style="text-align:center;"><img src="/images/posts/2024-08-21/new-main.jpg" width="240px"><p><font size="1"><i>In with the new!!!</i></font></p></div></div>
            <p>Now you may be wondering what all has changed. Rest assured, I have compiled a list of as many changes as I bothered to keep track of throughout the development of this site update. Let’s start with…</p>
            
            <h2>The iframe Container</h2>
            <p>The biggest change I’ve made to the site is the iframe container. Everything has been overhauled on this, from the background to the contents of the primary container itself.</p>
            
            <p>Let’s start with the banner. The site page links on the banner are now contained in boxes, and they now light up and make noise whenever you hover over or click them!! The <i>ConnorTheVGFan78</i> logo has received a color swap, and right beside it is the brand new Random Banner Image (more on that later).</p>
            
            <p>The footer has been cleaned up a bit. All of the buttons that are already on the landing page have been removed from the footer (kinda redundant having them in both places).</p>
            
            <h2>Random Banner Images</h2>
            
            <p>Every time the iframe container is loaded, a Random Banner Image will be selected and displayed. These images are random screenshots that I have taken within various games that I’ve played.</p>
            
            <p>If you click on the Banner Image, you will be taken to a master list of Random Banner Images. I plan on implementing individual pages for each image in the future, but since there’s only three of them at the moment, it doesn’t hurt to just show all of them at the same time.</p>
            
            <h2>The Home Page</h2>
            
            <p>Let’s be honest, the Home Page prior to this update was a disorganized mess. This update has changed that. Every square pixel is now being used to its full potential.</p>
            
            <p>The disclaimers that are now covered in the landing page have been removed from the home page. I found that it’s awfully redundant to have the same warnings told to you twice.</p>
            
            <p>The welcome message is now front and center instead of being off to the side.</p>
            
            <p>The current status section has received a few minor changes, but the main change I would like to point out is the new .beat time clock. You can learn how .beat time works on <a href="https://wiki.melonland.net/swatch_time" target="_blank">this page at the MelonLand Wiki</a>.</p>
            
            <p>The changelog has moved to the bottom of the page, with some minor cosmetic changes. And speaking of cosmetic changes…</p>
            
            <h2>Sitewide Appearance</h2>
            
            <p>As you may have noticed, every single page on the site has received a cosmetic update. A few major changes were made to the site’s master style sheet. I won’t go into too much detail, so here’s a few highlights:</p>
            <ul style="text-align: left;">
            <li>Changed the background of every page to stars.gif. This was originally only the Sitemap and Landing page backgrounds, but I love it too much to confine it to just two pages.</li>
            <li>Text now has a drop shadow for extra detail.</li>
            <li>Enhanced compatibility for lower-resolution monitors</li>
            <li>Basic compatibility for mobile devices. This doesn’t mean the site is going to be 100% mobile friendly, I’m just making things a little more tolerable for those who use the glass rectangle instead of a PC.</li>
            </ul>
            
            <p>And thus concludes this long list of changes to the site. I worked very hard on these changes and I hope you all enjoy them. If you have any comments or concerns, feel free to use the Chatbox on the Home Page, DM me on Discord (connorthevgfan78), or e-mail me (connor[at-symbol]connorthevgfan78.com).</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2024 09:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <link>https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/posts/2024-08-21-Wow--a-MAJOR-UPDATE---.html</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/feed.xml#1</guid>
  </item>

  <item>
    <title>First, lol</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p>Well, here it is. The first in what I hope to be many upon many blog posts to this website. With this being posted here, I officially retire the blog on my <a href="https://connorthevgfan78.wordpress.com/" target="_blank">Wordpress</a> site.</p>

<p>In fact, I might as well retire the <a href="https://connorthevgfan78.wordpress.com/" target="_blank">Wordpress</a> site permanently. It has been gathering dust for the past however long it’s been since I last updated it. It has served its purpose, and for that, I bid it farewell.<p>
<img src="/images/posts/2024-07-27/img-01.png">
<p class="caption">Goodnight, sweet prince. You will hardly be missed.</p>
<p>With that out of the way, welcome to the brand new and somewhat-improved home of the ConnorTheVGFan78 blog. And yes, if that name becomes too much of a mouthful, you can just call me Connor.</p>
<p>Now you may be wondering to yourselves:</p>
  
<p><i>“Connor, what exciting plans do you have for this blog???”</i></p>
  
<p>…I wish I knew, lol. This is basically a place where I can post about different things that I’m interested in, things I’m doing, as well as discoveries I’ve made during my journey throughout the web.</p>
  
<p>And yeah, that’s pretty much it. I welcome you all to my blog and I hope you all enjoy reading whatever it is I post here!!!</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 July 2024 03:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <link>https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/posts/2024-07-27-First--lol.html</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/feed.xml#0</guid>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>
