<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
  <title>ConnorTheVGFan78's Blog</title>
  <description>A blog created by ConnorTheVGFan78</description>
  <link>https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/</link>
  <atom:link href="https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 23:31:19 -0400</lastBuildDate>
  <ttl>60</ttl>

<!-- ADD NEW POST HERE -->

  <item>
    <title>First, lol</title>
    <description>
<![CDATA[<p>Well, here it is. The first in what I hope to be many upon many blog posts to this website. With this being posted here, I officially retire the blog on my <a href="https://connorthevgfan78.wordpress.com/" target="_blank">Wordpress</a> site.</p>

<p>In fact, I might as well retire the <a href="https://connorthevgfan78.wordpress.com/" target="_blank">Wordpress</a> site permanently. It has been gathering dust for the past however long it’s been since I last updated it. It has served its purpose, and for that, I bid it farewell.<p>
<img src="/images/posts/2024-07-27/img-01.png">
<p class="caption">Goodnight, sweet prince. You will hardly be missed.</p>
<p>With that out of the way, welcome to the brand new and somewhat-improved home of the ConnorTheVGFan78 blog. And yes, if that name becomes too much of a mouthful, you can just call me Connor.</p>
<p>Now you may be wondering to yourselves:</p>
  
<p><i>“Connor, what exciting plans do you have for this blog???”</i></p>
  
<p>…I wish I knew, lol. This is basically a place where I can post about different things that I’m interested in, things I’m doing, as well as discoveries I’ve made during my journey throughout the web.</p>
  
<p>And yeah, that’s pretty much it. I welcome you all to my blog and I hope you all enjoy reading whatever it is I post here!!!</p>]]>
    </description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 July 2024 03:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <link>https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/posts/2024-07-27-First--lol.html</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.connorthevgfan78.com/feed.xml#0</guid>
  </item>

</channel>
</rss>
